[
    {
        "Question":"An algebraic expression containing three terms is called a",
        "Options":[
            "monomial",
            "binomial",
            "trinomial",
            "all of these"
        ],
        "CorrectOption":2,
        "MarksAllocated":1,
        "DifficultyLevel":"Easy"
    },
    {
        "Question":"Number of terms in the expression $$3.x^2.y - 2.y^2.z - z^2.x + 5$$ is",
        "Options":[
            "2",
            "3",
            "4",
            "5"
        ],
        "CorrectOption":2,
        "MarksAllocated":1,
        "DifficultyLevel":"Easy"
    },
    {
        "Question":"The terms of expression $$4.x^2 - 3.x.y$$ are:",
        "Options":[
            "$$4.x^2$$ and $$-3.x.y$$",
            "$$4.x^2$$ and $$3.x.y$$",
            "$$4.x^2$$ and $$-x.y$$",
            "$$x^2$$ and $$x.y$$"
        ],
        "CorrectOption":0,
        "MarksAllocated":1,
        "DifficultyLevel":"Easy"
    },
    {
        "Question":"Factors of $$-5.x^2.y^2.z$$ are",
        "Options":[
            "$$-5.x.y.z$$",
            "$$-5.x^2.y.z$$",
            "$$-5.x.x.y.y.z$$",
            "$$-5.x.y.z^2$$"
        ],
        "CorrectOption":2,
        "MarksAllocated":1,
        "DifficultyLevel":"Medium"
    },
    {
        "Question":"Coefficient of x in $$-9.x.y^2.z$$ is",
        "Options":[
            "$$9.y.z$$",
            "$$-9.y.z$$",
            "$$9.y^2.z$$",
            "$$-9.y^2.z$$"
        ],
        "CorrectOption":3,
        "MarksAllocated":1,
        "DifficultyLevel":"Medium"
    },
    {
        "Question":"The subtraction of 5 times of y from x is",
        "Options":[
            "$$5x - y$$",
            "$$y - 5x$$",
            "$$x - 5y$$",
            "$$5y - x$$"
        ],
        "CorrectOption":2,
        "MarksAllocated":1,
        "DifficultyLevel":"Easy"
    },
    {
        "Question":"The side length of the top of a square table is x. The expression for perimeter is:",
        "Options":[
            "$$4 + x$$",
            "2x",
            "4x",
            "8x"
        ],
        "CorrectOption":2,
        "MarksAllocated":1,
        "DifficultyLevel":"Medium"
    },
    {
        "Question":"The expression for the number of diagonals that we can make from one vertex of a n sided polygon is:",
        "Options":[
            "$$2n + 1$$",
            "$$n - 2$$",
            "$$5n + 2$$",
            "$$n - 3$$"
        ],
        "CorrectOption":3,
        "MarksAllocated":1,
        "DifficultyLevel":"Hard"
    },
    {
        "Question":"$$123.x^2.y - 138.x^2.y$$ is a like term of",
        "Options":[
            "$$10.x.y$$",
            "$$-15.x.y$$",
            "$$-15.x.y^2$$",
            "$$10.x^2.y$$"
        ],
        "CorrectOption":3,
        "MarksAllocated":1,
        "DifficultyLevel":"Hard"
    },
    {
        "Question":"The value of $$3.x^2 - 5.x + 3$$ when x = 1 is",
        "Options":[
            "1",
            "0",
            "-1",
            "11"
        ],
        "CorrectOption":0,
        "MarksAllocated":1,
        "DifficultyLevel":"Easy"
    },
    {
        "Question":"$$ (2^{20} \u00f7 2^{15}) \u00d7 2^3 = $$",
        "Options":[
            "$$2^15$$",
            "$$2^8$$",
            "$$2^5$$",
            "None of these"
        ],
        "CorrectOption":1,
        "MarksAllocated":1,
        "DifficultyLevel":"Hard"
    },
    {
        "Question":"$$ (5\/6)^0 = $$",
        "Options":[
            "1",
            "$$6\/5$$",
            "0",
            "None of these"
        ],
        "CorrectOption":0,
        "MarksAllocated":1,
        "DifficultyLevel":"Easy"
    },
    {
        "Question":"$$ (2^2)^n = (2^3)^4$$, then n = ",
        "Options":[
            "4",
            "3",
            "12",
            "6"
        ],
        "CorrectOption":3,
        "MarksAllocated":1,
        "DifficultyLevel":"Medium"
    },
    {
        "Question":"$$(-7\/5)^{(-1)} = $$",
        "Options":[
            "5\/7",
            "-5\/7",
            "7\/5",
            "None of these"
        ],
        "CorrectOption":1,
        "MarksAllocated":1,
        "DifficultyLevel":"Medium"
    },
    {
        "Question":"$$ 81^5 \u00f7 (3^2)^5 = $$",
        "Options":[
            "$$3^{10}$$",
            "$$3^2$$",
            "$$3^5$$",
            "None of these"
        ],
        "CorrectOption":0,
        "MarksAllocated":1,
        "DifficultyLevel":"Medium"
    },
    {
        "Question":"$$ (8^2 \u00d7 8^4) - 2^{(18)} = $$",
        "Options":[
            "$$2^2$$",
            "$$2^4$$",
            "0",
            "None of these"
        ],
        "CorrectOption":2,
        "MarksAllocated":1,
        "DifficultyLevel":"Hard"
    },
    {
        "Question":"$$ (3^7) \u00f7 (81 \u00d7 3^3) = $$",
        "Options":[
            "$$3$$",
            "$$3^2$$",
            "$$3^0$$",
            "None of these"
        ],
        "CorrectOption":2,
        "MarksAllocated":1,
        "DifficultyLevel":"Hard"
    },
    {
        "Question":"$$ (1\/4)^{-3} - (1\/3)^{-3} = $$",
        "Options":[
            "$$37$$",
            "$$1\/37$$",
            "$$-37$$",
            "$$-1\/37$$"
        ],
        "CorrectOption":0,
        "MarksAllocated":1,
        "DifficultyLevel":"Medium"
    },
    {
        "Question":"$$ (10 \u00d7 5^{(n+1)}+ 25 \u00d7 5^n) \u00f7 (3 \u00d7 5^({n+2)}+ 10 \u00d7 5^(n+1)) $$",
        "Options":[
            "$$3\/5$$",
            "1",
            "0",
            "5"
        ],
        "CorrectOption":0,
        "MarksAllocated":1,
        "DifficultyLevel":"Hard"
    },
    {
        "Question":"$$ (-1)^{50} \u00d7 (-1)^{51} \u00d7 (1)^{100} \u00d7 (-1)^{101} = $$",
        "Options":[
            "-1",
            "1",
            "0",
            "2"
        ],
        "CorrectOption":1,
        "MarksAllocated":1,
        "DifficultyLevel":"Easy"
    },
    {
        "Question":"Find the mode for the data set, which shows the heights( in inches ) of 10 students in a class: 60, 65, 63, 62, 65, 70, 62, 68, 60, 65",
        "Options":[
            "62",
            "65",
            "70",
            "60"
        ],
        "CorrectOption":1,
        "MarksAllocated":1,
        "DifficultyLevel":"Hard"
    }
]
